Hey guys, so today I'll be breaking down this ad
that I shared yesterday in the ad in Per channel.
And by the end of this video you'll have a
recipe for a winning ad. So let's begin.
Once you get these, you'll never buy another pan
again, not
So this right here is the hook for this ad.
And with the hook, it's both a auditory and a visual hook.
So in the voiceover he goes, like, once you get these,
you never buy another pan again, just
with the beginning five seconds of this ad,
we already have a premise of
what this ad is going to be about.
We already know what the product is,
we already know the problem and the solution.
So this is a really powerful hook that they're using.
And for the visuals there, there are two shots
of this disgusting pan, which is kind of a pattern interrupt
and it's, it instantly makes you think like, oh,
what is going on here?
So they use this and this is also the problem
that people are facing that their product solves.
And the other two shots are shots of their pan,
which looks pretty.
This guy is putting oil on it
and then they're cracking an egg on it, which instantly
shows what they're talking about.
It's, oh, nothing is gonna stick on this
pan, which is the problem.
And then they move on to the pain points.
And again, non-stick pans are
expensive and scratch easily.
And stainless steel pans cause food
to stick cast iron pans can get sticky
and gross when used wrong. Heck.
And now they talked about the pain points.
They went like, oh, non-stick pans have this problem.
Stainless steel pans have this problem,
cast iron pans have this problem.
And for the visuals they were using,
I really like these two shots,
which is this guy scratching a non-stick pan with a fork.
I think it's really engaging to watch.
And then they show another disgusting pan, which is also
linked to what they're saying.
So their visual and the audio is really linked together.
It's another pan, it's a stainless steel pan
that is causing food to stick.
And the next shot they use is
also a cast and pan.
And the problem that, oh, it can get sticky and gross
and the visual is really gross.
So these were the pain points they high highlighted.
So, so far they started with the hook
and then they moved on to the pain points.
So now we already know the preface of the video.
We already know in a little more depth that
what is the problem that you are facing
and now they go on to give the solution.
Hex clad cookware is the best of non-stick,
stainless steel and cast iron in one pan.
Now it's uh, them explaining their
product in five seconds.
Really quick is, oh our pan, it's the best of non-stick,
stainless steel and cast iron.
All the ones that we showed you have different problems.
Ours is a mix of all and it's the best one.
This is the solution we have for you.
And now they double down on their
solution is they go onto the features.
What are the features that our pan offers?
Expat's hybrid technology has the durability of cast iron,
the flexibility of non-stick
and the searing power of stainless steel.
It's oven saved dishwasher seed.
So these were all the features of their pan.
And it was, oh, it is durable as cast iron.
It is flexible as a non-stick
and it has the searing power of stainless steel.
So they're really solving each problem that they showed
before and showing
how their product solves all these problems.
And now we have the pain points, we have the solution
and we have all the features of the solution.
Now they talk about what you gain from this.
They talk about the benefits of this span.
I get compliments whenever I cook from my friends,
I use it every day.
And this is what you gain for anybody cooking,
which is their target audience is the best thing
that could happen to you is people
complimenting what you cooked.
And in the visual, they have a shot of this guy that, uh,
that is using their pan
and he is really happy, really smiling, the music uplifted
and they really tell you that, okay, this is
what you gain from getting a a, it's emotional
and I think this worked really well for them.
And once you had they showcase the benefits,
then they went down to their offer. Yeah,
And I got 33% off when I bought mine.
They even have a lifetime guarantee.
So you know it's worth every pay.
Now they put a no-brainer offer on the table.
It's oh, it's 33% off on the span
and you get a lifetime guarantee.
So if you were not sold already,
now they double down on the value proposition
and they were like, oh, we give you a big discount,
which is adding value
and now we also give you a lifetime guarantee,
which is adding more value.
I threw out all my other pans once I got these
And then the guy goes like, oh,
I threw out all my other pans once I got these.
So it was kind of a indirect call to action is, okay,
you'll need to throw out all your other
pans and get this pen.
And then they have a visual call to action
with all the info in the end.
So this right here is a winning ad
to put everything together.
They start with the hook, they go to the pain points,
they give the solution, then they go to the features of
what features solve, what pain point, then they go to,
what do you gain from it, the benefits.
And then they put a offer on the table,
which you don't have to think about.
And then they put a indirect call to action
and then you have a clear call to action that, oh,
you can shop for this pan, this is our brand.
They have a logo animation going on
and if you shop, you get up to 30% off.
So this was my breakdown for this ad.
I hope you guys found it valuable
and I'll see you again in a few days with more new content.